(Howard:)she certainly has spent
her fair share of time
(Howard:)around what we can assume was
pretty massive weaponry.
(Bernadette:)I think Mr. Wolowitz
needs to keep in mind
(Bernadette:)that the past
is the past.
But he should know
that I am the kind of girl
who could get all
the giant missiles she wants.
(Amy:)Are we talking about women
wanting penises?
(Amy:)Because I'd like to weigh in.
(Sheldon:)Dr. Koothrappali, would you care
to join the conversation?
(Howard:)Certainly.
I'd like to raise two points.
Number one, I think they are
talking about penises.
(Raj:)And number two, these mimosas
are kicking my little brown ass.
(Leonard:)I'd like to kick
your little brown ass.
(Raj:)What did I do?